Guide to the Student writings collection ARCH088
University of Hartford Archives & Special Collections
Student writings collection
1962 - 2000
University of Hartford Archives & Special Collections
ARCH088
2.54 Linear Feet (7 containers)
Conditions Governing Access
The collection is open to all researchers. The Touchstone file does contain a FERPA restricted folder (Box 6, Folder 10).
Scope and Contents
The collection includes a number of student publications which were short-lived and/or no longer produced. Longer running or currently active student publications may have their own collections.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by publication in alphabetical order.
Related Materials
Aerie collection (ARCH164); Student newspaper collection (ARCH143); Hartbeat collection (ARCH166)
Periodicals; Student publications; University of Hartford
- Barrier, 1962 May 5 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Blank, 1978 Jan - 1978 May (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Conception, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Dancing Backwards, 1983 Dec (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Fitzgerald at the Vanguard, 1983 Mar (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Explorations, 1979 Apr - 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7-15, Box 2, Folder 1-13)
- Expressions, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- From the Workshop, 1983 - 1985 (Box 2, Folder 15 - 16, Box 3, Folder 1 - 2)
- Fuze, 1966 May (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Golgatha Review, 1968 Apr 4 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Hog River, 1967 - 1976, undated (Box 3, Folder 5 - 13, Box 4, Folder 1, Box Shared Small Oversized 1)
- Liberated Press, 1969 May (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Little Hog, 1973 Dec - 1978 Mar (Box 4, Folder 3 - 14)
- New Paper, 1972 - 1973 (Box 4, Folder 15 - 16)
- Nexus, 1970 May (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Pen in Hand, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Sightings, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Spectrum, 1980 - 1991 (Box 5, Folder 3 - 11)
- Substitute, 1972 - 1976 (Box 5, Folder 12 - 16)
- Syzygy, 1995 - 1997 (Box 5, Folder 17 - 19)
- Touchstone, 1963 Jan - 1966 Apr (Box 6, Folder 1 - 10)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Box 6, Folder 10 is restricted in accordance to archives restriction policy regarding FERPA protected records.
- U.H. Liberated News, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)